final List<Map<String, dynamic>> allQuestions = [
  {
    "question":
        "What is the programming language used to develop Flutter apps?",
    "options": ["Dart", "Kotlin", "Swift", "Java"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which widget is used to create a scrollable list in Flutter?",
    "options": ["Column", "Row", "ListView", "Stack"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the default file extension for Flutter project files?",
    "options": [".dart", ".flutter", ".dartproj", ".flut"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which command is used to create a new Flutter project?",
    "options": [
      "flutter new",
      "flutter create",
      "flutter init",
      "flutter build"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question":
        "What is the name of Flutterâ€™s state management library developed by Google?",
    "options": ["Redux", "Bloc", "Provider", "MobX"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which widget is used to handle user input in Flutter?",
    "options": ["Text", "Image", "TextField", "Container"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main function in Flutter used for?",
    "options": [
      "Initialize variables",
      "Start the app",
      "Build the UI",
      "Handle user input"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question":
        "Which widget allows you to add padding around other widgets in Flutter?",
    "options": ["Container", "Padding", "Margin", "Align"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question":
        "What is the purpose of the `pubspec.yaml` file in a Flutter project?",
    "options": [
      "Define dependencies",
      "Define UI layout",
      "Handle state management",
      "Define routes"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question":
        "Which widget is used to manage navigation between screens in Flutter?",
    "options": ["Navigator", "Route", "Stack", "Scaffold"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
];
